复习练习二：你是坚定型还是随性型？请回答下面这些
Review exercise two, are you steadfast or freewheeling? Answer the following
问题，并在相应的方框里打勾。第一，你
questions with a check mark in the appropriate box. Number one, would you
更愿意回答论文题还是选择题？第二，你
rather answer an essay question or a multiple choice question? Number two, do
是先从 yes 开始还是先从 no 开始？第三，你更喜欢
you start from yes or start from no? Number three, do you prefer solutions that
开放式、抽象、可以解释的方案，还是清晰、精确、客观的方案？第四，你
are open-ended, abstract, and subject to interpretation or clear-cut, precise, and
能否接受更灵活的时间安排并持续更新，还是更偏
objective? Number four, are you comfortable with a flexible time frame
向有截止日期的安排？第五，你更愿意
with constant updates or more deadline-oriented? Number five, do you prefer to
跟随别人的带领，还是按自己的方式做事？如果你选择了第二
follow another person's lead or do things your own way? If you selected the second
种选项两次或更多次，试试这个练习。就在今天，
option two or more times, try this experiment. Just for today, when someone
当别人对你说话时，练习暂时搁置判断，回复
says something to you, practice temporarily suspending judgment. Respond
“嗯，有意思，再多说一点。”或者“你也可能是对的。”这样做有两个好处：
with, hmm, that's interesting. Tell me more or you could be right. Not only will
首先会帮助你更好地倾听，也会让你成为更好的对话者，
this help you listen better, it will also make you a better conversationalist and
让你更容易吸收并使用这种口音。
open your mind to picking up and using this accent.